const allQuestions = [
    { question: 'What happens in cystic fibrosis in the lungs?', options: ['lungs become larger', 'mucus gets stuck in the lungs', 'lungs turn blue', 'new lungs grow'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'What does mucus look like in the lungs?', options: ['dry', 'liquid like water', 'thick and sticky', 'like dust'], answer: 2 },
    { question: 'What makes it difficult to breathe with cystic fibrosis?', options: ['too much mucus', 'too much air', 'lungs do not move', 'nose is blocked'], answer: 0 },
    { question: 'Who helps with cystic fibrosis?', options: ['a painter', 'a firefighter', 'a doctor', 'an astronaut'], answer: 2 },
    { question: 'What can you do to breathe better?', options: ['take medication', 'eat lots of sweets', 'sleep more', 'dont speak'], answer: 0 },
    { question: 'Which lung is healthy in the picture?', options: ['the right lung', 'neither', 'both', 'the left one'], answer: 3 },
    { question: 'What does the word “genetic” mean?', options: ['something you buy', 'something you inherit', 'something learned in school', 'something that disappears in the body'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'Why is it important to clear mucus in the lungs?', options: ['to make lungs bigger', 'to not feel like eating sweets', 'to breathe better', 'to keep skin clean'], answer: 2 },
    { question: 'What does the picture show about the lungs?', options: ['explains how lungs stay healthy', 'difference between healthy and diseased lung', 'explains how mucus is produced', 'shows why lungs are blue'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'Why is it important to know about diseases like cystic fibrosis?', options: ['so we can dance better', 'so we can eat more sweets', 'so we dont have to buy shoes', 'so we can help ourselves and others'], answer: 3 },
    { question: 'What is the role of physiotherapy in cystic fibrosis?', options: ['to build muscles', 'to help remove mucus', 'to make lungs larger', 'to clean the skin'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'What is one challenge people with cystic fibrosis face?', options: ['finding new shoes', 'trouble breathing', 'having too many lungs', 'eating only sweets'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'Why is regular exercise important in cystic fibrosis?', options: ['to strengthen lungs', 'to increase mucus', 'to stop coughing', 'to turn lungs blue'], answer: 0 },
    { question: 'What does a special diet do for people with cystic fibrosis?', options: ['makes lungs bigger', 'helps maintain energy', 'makes mucus disappear forever', 'changes lung color'], answer: 1 },
    { question: 'What does medication do for people with cystic fibrosis?', options: ['removes all mucus instantly', 'helps breathe better and reduce infections', 'makes you run faster', 'turns lungs red'], answer: 1 }
  ];
  
  export default allQuestions;
  